unicode.com 2014-08-22

# Privacy Policy | Sphere WMS

SphereWMS respects your concern for privacy. We recognize that we have an important responsibility to protect the privacy and security of the non-public personal information that we collect from you.

The following Privacy Policy describes the non-public information that we collect, in what cases that we may share such information with others, and our policies and practices with respect to protecting the confidentiality and security of such information. If you have any questions, please call us at 800-345-8498.

The types of information we collect:

We collect non-public personal information about you from the following sources:

Information we receive from you on applications or other forms; and

Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates or others.

This may include information such as your name, address, telephone numbers,

fax numbers, e-mail addresses or employee identification numbers.

Disclosure of non-public personal information:

We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers that we collect, as described above, except as permitted by law.

Confidentiality and Security:

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide and administer products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your non-public personal information.
